# MITCHELL R. DORSEY

5793 Opengate Court, Cincinnati, OH 45247

(513) 203-3344 -- Github: https://github.com/mitchdorsey

Email: mitchellrdorsey@gmail.com -- LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/mitchelldorsey/

# PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Junior developer searching for a role that allows me to use my adaptability and communication skills. Constantly yearning to broaden my skill set both technologically and mentally. Past work experiences have given me strengths in thinking on my feet and continuously being flexible. Programmer that enjoys collaborating and contributing to a resourceful team.

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

C#/.Net	Git	SQL	jQuery	HTML5
Ajax	MS Unit	CSS3	ASP.Net MVC	unit testing
TDD	integration testing	ASP.Net MVC5	Bootstrap	Javascript

# **EDUCATION**

Tech Elevator - Cincinnati, Ohio

September 2018 - Present

14-week .NET coding bootcamp learning database programming, .NET frameworks and design patterns, web application security, server side programming and client side web programming (Javascript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Web services, JSON, XML)

Cincinnati State - Cincinnati, Ohio

September 2017 - May 2018

Studied Electrical Engineering Technology including learning to operate Digital Multimeter(DMM) tool to read volts, amps and resistance of electrical current

## **TECHNICAL EXPERIENCE**

## **Vending Machine Software**

• Developed in C# using OOP and file.io simulating a vending machine on CLI

#### **National Park Campsite Reservation**

- Developed in C# using OOP and SQL database of National Parks
- Allows user to navigate database and book reservations for a particular campsite

#### **National Park Weather Service**

Web application developed in C#/.Net using ASP.Net MVC5 pattern

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Lynch Imports - Sunman, Indiana

April 2014 - Present

# **Inventory Specialist**

- Received recognition by name from multiple customers regarding workplace positivity and valuing customers' time
- Continuously learning a variety of new technical and mechanical skills
- Apply practical reasoning and critical thinking with team members to determine course of action for inventory consolidation across many storage locations
- Factor numerous industry regulations into decision making on a daily basis

## King's Island Amusement Park - Mason, Ohio

March 2010 - August 2012

## Admissions Associate

- Earned exceptional marks in each end-of-summer evaluation, notably organizational skills
- Successfully orchestrated over \$10,000 in daily sales transactions
- Consistently kept a level head during fast-paced, high stress situations